Her grace changed the world. Her courage lit the way.
Mary is a drama, history, action film directed by D.J. Caruso.
A miraculous conception.
A merciless king.
A murderous pursuit.
Mary's journey to give birth to Jesus unfolds in
this biblical coming-of-age epic.
Mary, played by Noa Cohen.
Joseph, played by Ido Tako.
King Herod, played by Anthony Hopkins.
Joachim, played by Ori Pfeffer.
Anne, played by Hilla Vidor.
Gabriel, played by Dudley O'Shaughnessy.
Mary is a 2024 epic biblical film directed by D.
Caruso from a screenplay by Timothy Michael Hayes.
It follows Mary, mother of Jesus, played by Noa Cohen, from her
childhood in Nazareth to the birth of Jesus.
The film also stars Ido Tako, Ori Pfeffer, Hilla Vidor,
Dudley O'Shaughnessy, and Anthony Hopkins.
It was released on Netflix on December 6, 2024.
The film explores themes of coming of age, christmas, jesus christ.
The tone is emotional.